It's going to take more than a miracle to save their mountain
Forest Warrior is a action, family film directed by Aaron Norris.
McKenna, the spirit of Tanglewood Forest, can
transform into a bear, a wolf or an eagle.
When a gang of evil lumberjacks led by Travis Thorne arrive in Tanglewood
to chop the forest down, McKenna cannot let this happen.
With his new friends, the Lords of Tanglewood, a band of children who
love to play in the forest, he battles Thorne and his gang.
Jedidiah McKenna, played by Chuck Norris.
Paul Carpio, played by William Sanderson.
Sheriff Ramsey, played by Max Gail.
Lewis Burdette, played by Michael Friedman.
Clovis Madison, played by Roscoe Lee Browne.
Brian Anderson, played by Jordan Brower.
Forest Warrior is a 1996 American adventure film starring Chuck
Norris and directed by Norris's brother Aaron Norris.
The film was released on direct-to-video in the
United States on November 5, 1996.
The film explores themes of martial arts, wolf, magic, eagle, fistfight.